# MARK HEIL

Location: Seattle, WA 98125 | Phone: 414-429-0564 | Email: Mark.heil1122@gmail.com
LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/mark-heil-89b82910b/ | GitHub: https://github.com/Merkraith
Portfolio: https://secret-wave-70417.herokuapp.com/

#### **SUMMARY**

Full Stack Web Developer with a background in Printing and Publishing with a dedication to making a presentable and polished finished product. Applies creative expertise and experience in identifying quality and the aesthetically pleasing to making a finished well polished product. Known to be reliable and strong attention to detail, no matter the complexity of the project. Earned a professional certificate in Full Stack Web Development

# TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML5, CSS, Javascript ES6

Libraries: ReactJS, JQuery, Handlebars.js

Databases: MySQL, MongoDB

Frameworks: Express/Node.js, ReactBootstrapJS, Material-UI, Bootstrap.js, Materialize, DraftJS

## **PROJECTS**

## **Parti Greetings**

https://github.com/MVP-Marketplace/Parti-App/ | https://floating-ocean-70452.herokuapp.com//

A new kind of digital experience to celebrate occasions

- Front-End role of utilizing React-Bootstrap CSS into the project following designs on a Figma.
- Back-End Role covering DraftJS Implementation.
- ReactJS, React-Bootstrap, Cloudinary API, DraftJs, EmailJS, MongoDB, Passport

#### **Find Next Gia**

https://github.com/Merkraith/Band-Tour-Manager/ | https://merkraith.github.io/Band-Tour-Manager/Project/
Uses API concert information and connects it with a Map API that would return the upcoming concert information to what the user searched for.

- Front-End role of utilizing Materialize CSS into the project and creating the interface.
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Express, Node

## EXPERIENCE

# Full-Stack-Web Developer, April 2021- Present

MakeltMVP Remote, USA

• Part of a web development team, managing a startup web app with other Bootcamp Graduates.

# Press Operator, 2016-2020

BCT Seattle Seattle, WA

- Learned to self-manage and increase efficiency methods for daily production.
- Further developed quality control skills and attention to detail

**Press Operator**, 2005 - 2016

Creative Converting / Innoware Clintonville/Menomonee Falls, WI

- Developed communication skills working with multiple departments, problem solving and attention to detail.
- Achieved Lead roles in team operations and pre-press departments.

### **EDUCATION**

Certificate in Full Stack Web Development: University of Washington, Seattle, WA Associate Degree in Printing and Publishing: Waukesha County Technical College: Pewaukee, WI